Were you smoking
during break?
You reek!
Should I
use chopsticks?
Forget that
Did you get a tattoo?
No, it's a sticker
I bought a ton
Wow
these look like s***
I'm going to get
a tattoo later
I'm trying out
a bunch of designs
Hey, Hong Il-tak!
What? What is it?
Isn't this one
perfect for you?
"Man Alone"
A lonely man
How about it?
Isn't it cool?
No! Stop it! Don't!
Stop it!
F***!
Just stay still!
I can't see it
so it's hard to clean
Is it gone?
Kim Hyeong-ju
that a**hole
Crazy b******!
Son of a b****
What are you doing?
Is it not coming off?
Hey, Hyeon-wu
Some b*******
played a prank on me
I can't believe
he saw me like this
There's no way
we can be friends
Turn around
I'll help you
Ah, Hyeon-wu
Ow, it hurts
Be gentle
S***
Hey, Hyeon-wu
It really hurts
Be a little gentle
Hey, hey
It's almost gone
-F***
-Hey
What are
those b******* doing?